Guide to the Burton Hall Papers WAG.087
Tamiment Library and Robert F. Wagner Labor Archives
- Series II: Union Democracy Cases, 67652
  - Subseries B: Construction, 377307
    - United Brotherhood of Carpenters & Joiners, 68358
      - Murphy, Michael v. Local 488; "Committee for Union Justice," "South Bronx Carpenters Association," 1978; Intra-Union Charges, 1979; "Vote for Murphy", 1978-1979; 68362 (Box 4, Folder 13)
      - Maritas, Theodore, District Council of Carpenters, Indictment; NY Carpenters Defense Literature, Jan, 1981, 68361 (Box 4, Folder 14)
      - Local 135, Intra-Union Charges, 1967; Local 257, Intra-Union Charges, 1973, 1967-1973; 68360 (Box 4, Folder 15)
      - District Council of Carpenters, Dental Plan Investigation, F. Hogan, 1963, 68359 (Box 4, Folder 16)
    - Laborers International Union of North America (LIUNA), 68346
      - Gentile, Joseph v. Plasterers' Tenders' Helpers, Local Union No. 759; New York Civil Court Index No. 37511; Complaint, Jan 6. 1966; Correspondence, 1966-68, 1966, 1968; 68357 (Box 4, Folder 17)
      - Ballot, Local 759 Election; Contract, J. Gentile, Business Manager, May 25 1968; Correspondence, Pension Fund, 68356 (Box 4, Folder 18)
      - Willie Barnes v Sanzo, Louis, Local 29, LIUNA; 79 Civ. 7070; Index (Partial); Certification, Honest Ballot Association, July 21, 1981; Correspondence, Attorney N. Guzman to B. Hall, Dec 23, 1981, 68355 (Box 4, Folder 19)
      - Docket No. 81-7890 Willie Barnes; Appellate Papers, Jan 11 1982; B. Hall Affirmation in Opposition to Motion for Stay, Aug 27, 1982; Typesetting for Writ of Certiorari, Oct 8, 1982, 68354 (Box 4, Folder 20)
      - Appellant's Brief (BH); Joint Index; Legal Research Notes, undated; 68353 (Box 4, Folder 21)
      - Barnes, Appellate Briefs; Petition for Writ of Certiorari, undated; 68352 (Box 4, Folder 22)
      - Petramale, Pasquale v LIUNA, Local 17; U.S. Supreme Court Brief of the Respondent in Opposition, (BH), 1984, 68351 (Box 4, Folder 23)
      - Bedeau, Lloyd v Local 147, LIUNA; Discharge Grievance, undated; 68350 (Box 4, Folder 24)
      - Pickett, Arthur, Local 147, LIUNA, undated; 68349 (Box 4, Folder 25)
      - Artuso, Frank v Local 1175, Grievance, Jan, 1974, 68348 (Box 4, Folder 26)
      - RULED OUT OF ORDER (R.O.O.R.), Rank & File Opposition Group; LIUNA Response, 1979-81, 1979-1981; 68347 (Box 4, Folder 27)
    - Steamfitters Enterprise Association, Local 638, 68339
      - Gould, Walter, v. Murray, Thomas, Pres., Local 638; Index No. 13333-1960; Progressive Association Newsletter; Plaintiffs' Trial Memorandum (BH), 1959-60, 1959, 1960; 68345 (Box 4, Folder 28)
      - Rios, George, Gunther, John, v. Local 638; 71 Civ. 847;EEOC & Gunther, John v. Local 638, Index, pp. 2-7;Correspondence, Apr 18, 1974, 68344 (Box 4, Folder 29)
      - NLRB Charges, Apr 20, 1974, 68343 (Box 4, Folder 30)
      - Statements of Individual Applicants; Notice of Appeal, Aug 16, 1974, 68342 (Box 4, Folder 31)
      - Correspondence, BH; Federal Supplement, Rios, Oct 2, 1974, 68341 (Box 4, Folder 32)
      - Brief of Plaintiff-Appellee EEOC; Decision, U.S. Court of Appeals, Je 24, 1975; Lists of Applicants, 68340 (Box 4, Folder 33)
    - United Association of Journeymen & Apprentices of the Plumbing & Pipe Fitting Industry, 68337
      - United Association, Local 696, undated; 68338 (Box 4, Folder 34)
    - Operating Engineers, 68334
      - Gates, Leroy et. al., v. Dalton, Ralph, Pres., Local 14-14B; 73 Civ. 375; Defendants' Reply Memorandum, Aug 27, 1974; Memorandum & Judicial Opinion, July 8, 1975, 1974, 1975; 68336 (Box 4, Folder 35)
      - Memorandum in Support of Class Notification, Aug 7 1975; Memorandum & Order, Nov 30, 1977, 1975, 1977; 68335 (Box 4, Folder 36)
    - International Brotherhood of Electricians, 68331
      - Eatz, Brian et. al., v. DME Unit, Local 3, IBEW; CV 83 0792/87-7835; Class Action Complaint, 1983; 68333 (Box 4, Folder 37)
      - Mar 2, 1983; Brief of Defendant-Appellee, The NY Racing Association Inc., Feb 3, 1986, 68332 (Box 4, Folder 38)
    - International Brotherhood of Painters & Allied Trades (IBPAT), 68161
      - Affiliation & Autonomous Locals Cases - Local 1511; Briefs, etc., 1955-61, 1955-1961; 68330 (Box 5, Folder 1)
      - Arnold, Frank, v. District Council 9; 76 Civ 2816 (CBM); Order to Show Cause; Affadavit, F. Arnold, Je 30, 1976, 68329 (Box 5, Folder 2)
      - Plaintiff's Memorandum of Law, undated; 68328 (Box 5, Folder 3)
      - Defendant's Motion to Dismiss; Affidavit, C. Blum, undated; 68327 (Box 5, Folder 4)
      - Motion to Intervene, BH, on Behalf of Local 490, July 1 1976; Memorandum in Support, 68326 (Box 5, Folder 5)
      - Court Papers, Nov. 1976 - Jan. 1977, 1976-1977; 68325 (Box 5, Folder 6)
      - Joint Industry Board, Ass. of Master Painters; NLRB Case, undated; 68324 (Box 5, Folder 7)
      - Barish, David v. District Council 9; Retirees Pension Rights, Aug 30. 1978; Plaintiff's FOIA, Oct 1, 1979, 1978, 1979; 68323 (Box 5, Folder 8)
      - Barish, D.; Pension Rights, Oct 1979; Mar 1980, 1979, 1980; 68322 (Box 5, Folder 9)
      - Bongiardina v. Schonfeld, 1972, Local 121, Astoria, 1974, 1972, 1974; 68321 (Box 5, Folder 10)
      - Burke v. Caputo, District Council 9, Je 1961, 68320 (Box 5, Folder 11)
      - Disciplinary Cases, District Council 9, undated; 68319 (Box 5, Folder 12)
      - French, D. v. Caputo, L. & Rarback, M. v. French, D., undated; 68318 (Box 5, Folder 13)
      - French, D. v. Shatz Painting, 1962-69, 1962-1969; 68317 (Box 5, Folder 14)
      - Fritsch & Rossiter v. District Council 9, 1972, 68316 (Box 5, Folder 15)
      - Giraldo v. Rosen, et. al. & District Council 9, 1972, 68315 (Box 5, Folder 16)
      - Gulickson v Forest; 65 Civ. 139; Complaint & Proposed Judgement, May, 1968, 68314 (Box 5, Folder 17)
      - Gulickson, Opinion, Je 19, 1968; & Order, Nov 12 1969, 1968, 1969; 68313 (Box 5, Folder 18)
      - IBPAT v, District Council 9; 77 Civ. 2108 (LPG); 1977 Trusteeship, Aug 4, 1977, 68312 (Box 5, Folder 19)
      - Notice of Motion, Sept 2, 1977; Local 490; Intervention; Memorandum of Understanding, 68311 (Box 5, Folder 20)
      - Affidavit, J. Wolford, Sept 8 1977; Complaint; Memorandum to Intervene, Sept 12, 1977, 68310 (Box 5, Folder 21)
      - Defendant's Memorandum in Opposition, undated; 68309 (Box 5, Folder 22)
      - Janovic Plaza v. Local 1815, 1980, 68308 (Box 5, Folder 23)
      - Kesselman, Simon, Local 442, undated; 68307 (Box 5, Folder 24)
      - Langenbacker, John & Co. Inc.; Carl Blum, NLRB Charges, undated; 68306 (Box 5, Folder 25)
      - Langenbacker, NLRB, undated; 68305 (Box 5, Folder 26)
      - L & L Painting; Joseph Fierman v, L & L & District Council 9; NLRB Charges, undated; 68304 (Box 5, Folder 27)
      - Margolies, Malinow & Stein v. Caputo, Rarback, 1962, 68303 (Box 5, Folder 28)
      - Paikin, M. et. al. v. Rarback, M., 1964, 68302 (Box 5, Folder 29)
      - People of NY v. M. Rarback, 1967; E. Topp, R. Fritsch v. M. Rarback & Contractors, 1974, 1967, 1974; 68301 (Box 5, Folder 30)
      - People of State of NY v F. Schonfeld; Joint Apprentice Committee, C. Blum, 1972, 68300 (Box 5, Folder 31)
      - Perlin, et. al. v Rarback, M., 1964, 68299 (Box 5, Folder 32)
      - Pisman v Webman, Local 442; Assault, 1961-62, 1961-1962; 68298 (Box 5, Folder 33)
      - Robins, H. v Rarback, M., May 31 1961; Correspondence, Nov 26 1962, 1961, 1962; 68297 (Box 5, Folder 34)
      - Robins v Rarback; 63 Civ. 1017 / 72-2009, Feb 11 1963; Correspondence,Aug 19 1963, 68296 (Box 5, Folder 35)
      - Court Papers, 1963, 68295 (Box 5, Folder 36)
      - Judicial Order Je 11 1963; Correspondence, Aug 30 1963, 68294 (Box 5, Folder 37)
      - Brief of Plaintiff-Appellee, Nov 9. 1964; Stipulation, 68293 (Box 5, Folder 38)
      - Supreme Court Papers, Oct, 1963, Jan 18. 1965, 1963, 1965; 68292 (Box 5, Folder 39)
      - Correspondence Je 1, 1965; Enclosure - Court of Appeals; Decision, Oct, 1963, 1963-1965; 68291 (Box 5, Folder 40)
      - Court Appearance, Transcript, pp. 1-137, Oct 15, 1970, 68290 (Box 5, Folder 41)
      - Transcript, pp. 138-328A, undated; 68289 (Box 5, Folder 42)
      - Rosen v District Council 9, Intra-Union Trial Papers, 1960, 68288 (Box 6, Folder 1)
      - Complaint & Court Papers, May-Je 1961, 68287 (Box 6, Folder 2)
      - Motions, 1961, 68286 (Box 6, Folder 3)
      - Appellate Papers, Brief & Reply, undated; 68285 (Box 6, Folder 4)
      - Defendant's Brief; Deposition, BH May 1964, 68284 (Box 6, Folder 5)
      - Rosen v District Council 9, Supplementary Documents, Flyers, undated; 68283 (Box 6, Folder 6)
      - Salzhandler, Solomon; Correspondence & Internal Charges, 1958-61, 1958-1961; 68282 (Box 6, Folder 7)
      - Salzhandler v Caputo; Court Papers, Documents, Je-Aug 1961, 68281 (Box 6, Folder 8)
      - Court Papers Jan-May 1962, 68280 (Box 6, Folder 9)
      - Pre-Trial & Post-Trial; Memoranda, 1962, 68279 (Box 6, Folder 10)
      - Appellate Papers, 1962, 68278 (Box 6, Folder 11)
      - Court Papers, Apr-Dec 1963, 68277 (Box 6, Folder 12)
      - Court Papers, 1964, 68276 (Box 6, Folder 13)
      - Court Papers, 1966-67, 1966-1967; 68275 (Box 6, Folder 14)
      - Court Papers, 1968-70, 1968-1970; 68274 (Box 6, Folder 15)
      - Correspondence, C. Summers, ACLU, etc., undated; 68273 (Box 6, Folder 16)
      - Evidence, Checks, etc., undated; 68272 (Box 6, Folder 17)
      - Appendix to Appellee's Brief & Petition for Writ of Certiorari; Printed Copies, Salzhandler Decision, undated; 68271 (Box 6, Folder 18)
      - Santos v Bonanno, (Woodfinishers); Complaint, Jan 1965; Answer, Feb 25, 1966; Correspondence, Je 6, 1974, 1965, 1974; 68270 (Box 6, Folder 19)
      - Motion for Preliminary Injunction, Jan 1966; Affidavits in Response, Feb 1966, 68269 (Box 6, Folder 20)
      - Appellate Papers, Briefs, undated; 68268 (Box 6, Folder 21)
      - Index & Appendix to Brief, undated; 68267 (Box 6, Folder 22)
      - Santos v District Council of Carpenters; NLRB, 1965-68, 1965-1968; 68266 (Box 6, Folder 23)
      - Santos v Carpenters; Telegram to S. F. Raftery, Mar 20, 1969; Affidavits, Woodfinishers, Aug 1969, 68265 (Box 6, Folder 24)
      - Determination, Impartial Umpire, Sept, 1969; Correspondence, Dec, 1969, 68264 (Box 6, Folder 25)
      - General Counsel Brief, NLRB; Correspondence, Nov 5, 1971, 68262 (Box 6, Folder 27)
      - Trial Examiner's Decision, NLRB; Correspondence, Nov 28, 1972, 68261 (Box 6, Folder 28)
      - Telegram to S. F. Raftery, Jan 17, 1973; Telegram to J. Shay, Dir. of Jurisdiction, AFL-CIO, 29-Nov-73, 68260 (Box 6, Folder 29)
      - District Council 9, Notice of Meeting Jan 22, 1974; Minutes (Page), Aug 20, 1974, 68259 (Box 6, Folder 30)
      - Correspondence, Frank Santos, Feb 4, 1975; Defendant's Memorandum in Reply, 68258 (Box 6, Folder 31)
      - Correspondence, Jan 6, 1976; Notice of Motion for Adjournment, 18-Oct-76, 68257 (Box 6, Folder 32)
      - Santos v Carpenters; Appellate Briefs, 1976, 68256 (Box 7, Folder 1)
      - Court of Appeals, in re Decision Jan, 1976; Memorandum in Opposition (Plaintiff), 68255 (Box 7, Folder 2)
      - Affidavit, M. Vozzo Jan 14, 1978; Affidavit, BH Je 5, 1978, 68254 (Box 7, Folder 3)
      - Deposition, F. Santos Je 13, 1978; Notice of Deposition Sept 14, 1978, 68253 (Box 7, Folder 4)
      - Pre-Trial Order Aug 6, 1979; Subpoena, J. Bishop, Apr 10, 1979, 68252 (Box 7, Folder 5)
      - Correspondence, Apr 20, 1979; Defendant's Post-Trial Memorandum, 68251 (Box 7, Folder 6)
      - Opinion, Metzner, D.J., May 11, 1979; Notice of Appeal, Sept 6, 1979, 68250 (Box 7, Folder 7)
      - Appellate Briefs, Index 1979, 68249 (Box 7, Folder 8)
      - Joint Appendices; Petition for Rehearing, undated; 68248 (Box 7, Folder 9)
      - Exhibits, Trade Ageements, undated; 68247 (Box 7, Folder 10)
      - Schonfeld, F. v Shatz Painting; NLRB, 1963, 68246 (Box 7, Folder 11)
      - Schonfeld v Rarback (Mailing Lists); 64 Civ. 1550; Candidate's Request for Lists; Motion for Discontinuance, Je 4, 1965, 68245 (Box 7, Folder 12)
      - Schonfeld v Rarback; 65 Civ. 2695; Memorandum, MacMahon, D.J., Oct 27, 1965; Plaintiff's Memorandum; in Opposition, 68244 (Box 7, Folder 13)
      - Notice of Motion, Je 1, 1966; Designation of BH or H. Easton as Trial Counsel Nov 20, 1967, 1966, 1967; 68243 (Box 7, Folder 14)
      - Workers Defense League Flyer, July 21, 1967; Correspondence to BH (Discontinuance v Arber) Dec 8, 1969, 1967, 1969; 68242 (Box 7, Folder 15)
      - Plaintiff's Memorandum after Trial, Jan 2, 1970; Opinion, McLean, D.J., Feb 19, 1970, 68241 (Box 7, Folder 16)
      - Schonfeld v Wirtz; 66 Civ. 558; Original Appeal to DoL Jan, 1965; Deposition, BH, Dec 12, 1966, 1965, 1966; 68240 (Box 7, Folder 17)
      - Correspondence, R. Morgenthau, Feb 1, 1967; BH, Dec 5, 1967, 68239 (Box 7, Folder 18)
      - Legal Correspondence, Briefs; LRRM - "Schonfeld v Wirtz", undated; 68238 (Box 7, Folder 19)
      - Schonfeld v. Raftery (Trusteeship); 67 Civ. 1361 / 31512; Trustees Report Jan 23, 1967; Research on Trusteeships, 68237 (Box 7, Folder 20)
      - Complaint; Affidavits (Plaintiffs & J. Damery); Order to Show Cause, undated; 68236 (Box 7, Folder 21)
      - Defendant's Answer; Plaintiff's Memorandum in Support of Preliminary Injunction, undated; 68235 (Box 7, Folder 22)
      - Motions in Opposition, undated; 68234 (Box 7, Folder 23)
      - Memoranda; Post-Hearing Supplemental Memoranda, undated; 68233 (Box 7, Folder 24)
      - Opinion, Frankel, D.J., Je 16, 1967, 68232 (Box 7, Folder 25)
      - Order to Show Cause, Je 21, 1967; Order, Frankel, D.J., Je 21, 1967; Notice of Appeal Je 21, 1967, 68231 (Box 8, Folder 1)
      - Order to Show Cause, Je 30, 1967; Plaintiff's Reply Memorandum, 68230 (Box 8, Folder 2)
      - Amicus Brief, Workers Defense League, July 26, 1967; Amicus Brief, NYCLU; Affidavit in Opposition, J. Damery, Sept 7, 1967, 68229 (Box 8, Folder 3)
      - Defendant-Appellees Brief; Appellees Sur Reply, undated; 68228 (Box 8, Folder 4)
      - Reply Brief of Appellants, undated; 68227 (Box 8, Folder 5)
      - Amicus Brief, Dept. of Labor; Exhibits; District Council 9 Newsletter Mar, 1967, 68226 (Box 8, Folder 6)
      - Court Orders for Election, Sept, 1967; Enclosures - Order, Sept, 1967; & Opinion Je 1967, 68225 (Box 8, Folder 7)
      - Correspondence, Campaign Literature, Certification of Election Results (Originals), undated; 68224 (Box 8, Folder 8)
      - Trial Transcript (Partial), May 16, 1967, 68223 (Box 8, Folder 9)
      - Transcript, pp. 1-100, Nov 3, 1966, 68222 (Box 8, Folder 10)
      - Transcript, pp. 101-275, undated; 68221 (Box 8, Folder 11)
      - Transcript, pp. 276-400, Nov 4, 1966, 68220 (Box 8, Folder 12)
      - Transcript, pp. 401-572A, undated; 68219 (Box 8, Folder 13)
      - Transcript, pp. 573-700, Nov 9, 1966, 68218 (Box 8, Folder 14)
      - Transcript, pp. 701-862, undated; 68217 (Box 8, Folder 15)
      - Exhibits - Defendants; with "Progressive Painter" Sept, 1967, 68216 (Box 8, Folder 16)
      - Exhibits - Plaintiff, undated; 68215 (Box 8, Folder 17)
      - Exhibits - Plaintiff, undated; 68214 (Box 8, Folder 18)
      - Exhibits - Plaintiff *** with District Council 9 Newspapers, undated; 68213 (Box 8, Folder 19)
      - Schonfeld, Frank v Rosen, Sam; (C. Blum, D. Barish,; Staff Pension Fund) 1971-73, 1971-1973; 68212 (Box 8, Folder 20)
      - Schonfeld v Penza; 72 Civ. 2837; (BH Attorney for D. Presser), 1972, 68211 (Box 8, Folder 21)
      - Schonfeld v Noschese, T., Pres.,; District Council 9, 1980, 68210 (Box 8, Folder 22)
      - Tackler v Rarback; (Intra-Union Charges), 1962-64, 1962-1964; 68209 (Box 8, Folder 23)
      - Topp v Rarback; Intra-Union Charges; Court Papers, Mar-Apr, 1963, 68208 (Box 8, Folder 24)
      - Court Papers, May, 1963; Deposition, M. Buonora, Esq., May 6, 1963; Plaintiff's Rule 9 (g) Statement, 68207 (Box 8, Folder 25)
      - Response to Plaintiff's Statement; Supplement to Defendant's Pre-Trial Memorandum, Dec, 1964, 68206 (Box 8, Folder 26)
      - Correspondence; Draft of Appellate Decision, 1966; BH Correspondence ("Dear WDL"); BH Correspondence to Raftery, Aug 27, 1970, 1966, 1970; 68205 (Box 8, Folder 27)
      - Winn, Sam v Rarback, M.; Intra-Union Charges; Summons Aug 20, 1962; Note of Issue for Trial, Sept 10, 1962, 68204 (Box 8, Folder 28)
      - Answer of District Council 9 to BH Affidavit (Dated Nov 20 1962), 68203 (Box 8, Folder 29)
      - Correspondence, Sample Ballot, Protest against Setting Aside Election,; Sam Winn, undated; 68202 (Box 8, Folder 30)
      - Hearing Transcript, Trial Board, District Council 9, pp. 1-93, 11-Oct-61, undated; 68200 (Box 8, Folder 32)
      - Transcript, pp. 94-184a, undated; 68199 (Box 8, Folder 33)
      - Yochim v Caputo; 51 Civ. 2223; Trial Board Report; Appeal & Correspondence (F. Schonfeld), undated; 68198 (Box 9, Folder 1)
      - Index; Complaint; Motion for Order to Show Cause; Affidavit, F. Schonfeld, Oct 6, 1962, 68197 (Box 9, Folder 2)
      - Opposing Affidavit, L. Caputo Oct 15, 1962; Notice of Motion Striking Defendant's Answer, Dec 28, 1962, 68196 (Box 9, Folder 3)
      - Memorandum in Support; Correspondence Jan 31, 1963, 68195 (Box 9, Folder 4)
      - Yochim & French v Caputo; Correspondence, D. French, Jan 31, 1963; Correspondence, M. Buonora, Feb 20, 1963, 68194 (Box 9, Folder 5)
      - Plaintiff's Motion to Reargue, Mar 5, 1963; Memorandum, Pre- Trial Conference, Dec 12, 1963, 68193 (Box 9, Folder 6)
      - Correspondence, Jan 23, 1964; Affidavit, M. Rarback, Jan 26, 1964, 68192 (Box 9, Folder 7)
      - Memoranda on Motion to Dismiss, undated; 68191 (Box 9, Folder 8)
      - Correspondence, BH Mar 3, 1964; District Council to Schonfeld, Je 1965, 1964, 1965; 68190 (Box 9, Folder 9)
      - Correspondence & IBPAT Documents; BH to M. Kempton, NY Post, Nov 12, 1961; "Is Rarbackism On the Ropes", 68189 (Box 9, Folder 10)
      - Internal Documents - 1; Employment Application, Election Stickers, Sample Ballots, undated; 68188 (Box 9, Folder 11)
      - Internal Documents - 2; By-Laws 1949, Local Union 803, 68187 (Box 9, Folder 12)
      - Internal Documents - 3; District Council 9, Minutes, Dec 12, 1951 - Apr 2, 1963, 1951-1963; 68186 (Box 9, Folder 13)
      - Internal Documents - 4; Minutes, Oct 6, 1964 - Dec 2, 1969, 1964-1969; 68185 (Box 9, Folder 14)
      - Internal Documents - 5; Minutes, May 18, 1971 - Mar 6, 1973, 1971-1973; 68184 (Box 9, Folder 15)
      - Internal Documents - 5(a); Minutes, Nov 20, 1973 - Mar 5, 1974, 1973-1974; 68183 (Box 9, Folder 16)
      - Internal Documents - 5(b); Minutes, Apr 2, 1974 - Aug 20, 1974, 68182 (Box 9, Folder 17)
      - Internal Documents - 7; Literature 1949-1960s; Union Democracy in Action No. 9 - Salzhandler, Apr, 1963, 1949-1969; 68180 (Box 9, Folder 19)
      - Internal Documents - 8; Literature 1960s; NY Law Journal - Salzhandler, July 23, 1963, 1960-1963; 68179 (Box 9, Folder 20)
      - Internal Documents - 9; Literature 1970s, 68178 (Box 9, Folder 21)
      - District Council 9 v N. Valis; Internal Charges, 1975; Correspondence, May 29, 1975, 68177 (Box 9, Folder 22)
      - Local 1011 - 1; Brennan, W., Pres. v. Brotherhood, July 12, 1910; Petition, F. Schonfeld v. S. Aronson, Pres., 68176 (Box 9, Folder 23)
      - Local 1011 - 2; Rank & File Literature, Je 17, 1963 - Oct 25, 1968, 1963-1968; 68175 (Box 9, Folder 24)
      - Local 490, Paperhangers; Voting Machines Clippings, Dec 18, 1950, 68174 (Box 9, Folder 25)
      - Local 1974 - Alfarone, J. v. Bernie Wolff Construction Corp.; No. 86-264; Oct, 1986, 68169 (Box 9, Folder 30)
      - Local 1974 - National Wall Systems, Inc., 1975-1979; 68165 (Box 9, Folder 34)
      - Local 1974 v. Operative Plasterers, 1976-1989; 68164 (Box 9, Folder 35)
      - Local 1974 v. Local 530, 1985; 68163 (Box 9, Folder 36)
  - Subseries C: Maritime, 377308
    - Marine Engineers Benevolent Association (MEBA), 68119
      - Calhoon, Jesse (Assault), 1963, 68160 (Box 10, Folder 1)
      - Cloud, Terry PROMEBAMEN.; Norfolk, District 1 1964, 68159 (Box 10, Folder 2)
      - Grasso, Larry, PROMEBAMEN,; Local 33, District #1, undated; 68158 (Box 10, Folder 3)
      - Jackson, Walter v. National; MEBA 63 Civ. 2226, undated; 68157 (Box 10, Folder 4)
      - Harvey, Raymond v. Calhoon, Jesse; 63 Civ. 2401; By-laws - District 1; Defendant Union's Memorandum for Motion to Dismiss, 1963, 68156 (Box 10, Folder 5)
      - Affidavit in Opposition, Aug 20, 1963; Deposition, Defendant's Attorney, Sept 30, 1963, 68155 (Box 10, Folder 6)
      - Correspondence, Nov 7, 1963; Calhoon Correspondence, Dec 20, 1963, 68154 (Box 10, Folder 7)
      - Plaintiff's Memorandum in Opposition to Defendant's Proposals; Affidavit, BH, Dec 31, 1963, 68153 (Box 10, Folder 8)
      - Correspondence, BH, Jan 3, 1964; Affidavit, L. Dodson, Mar 17, 1964, 68152 (Box 10, Folder 9)
      - Correspondence, Mar 17, 1964; Order, USDJ Wyatt, Apr 6, 1964, 68151 (Box 10, Folder 10)
      - Correspondence, BH, Apr 6, 1964; Correspondence, Dec 11, 1964, 68150 (Box 10, Folder 11)
      - Judicial Order, Jan, 1965; Correspondence, Apr 19, 1965, 68149 (Box 10, Folder 12)
      - Correspondence, Law Review; Correspondence, H. Benson to BH, undated; 68148 (Box 10, Folder 13)
      - Appellate Briefs; Petition for Certiorari, undated; 68147 (Box 10, Folder 14)
      - Amici Curiae, undated; 68146 (Box 10, Folder 15)
      - Horner, Louis MEBA: No. 97, West Coast, Resolution# 35, May 20, 1957; Complaint, Dec 12, 1963; Correspondence, Dec 19, 1963, 1957, 1963; 68145 (Box 10, Folder 16)
      - Local 33 Opposition to Restructuring, Port of New York, 1959; Correspondence, Apr 3, 1961; Correspondence, BH, May 17, 1963, 1959, 1963; 68144 (Box 10, Folder 17)
      - Trial of Dewey Hueston, Mobile, AL, Correspondence, Dec 20, 1961; Affirmation of Trial Committee, May 21, 1962, 1961, 1962; 68143 (Box 10, Folder 18)
      - National MEBA Election 1963, Election Ballots/Campaign Flyers, 68142 (Box 10, Folder 19)
      - New Orleans MEBA, Dues Increase, Election, 1963, 68141 (Box 10, Folder 20)
      - Norfolk MEBA, Merger, undated; 68140 (Box 10, Folder 21)
      - Norfolk, Right of Officials to Hold Two Offices, undated; 68139 (Box 10, Folder 22)
      - Pacific Coast District, Professional, Office Affiliate, undated; 68138 (Box 10, Folder 23)
      - Rodway, George (PROMEBAMEN) Resolution, undated; 68136 (Box 10, Folder 25)
      - Roman, John v. Calhoon - MEBA; 14501/1963 Civ.; Election Challenge Stipulation, Oct 3, 1963; Deposition, BH; with Exhibit A, Sept 7, 1963, 68135 (Box 10, Folder 26)
      - Memorandum in Support of Motion for Preliminary Injunction; Judicial Order, Sept 16, 1963, 68134 (Box 10, Folder 27)
      - Correspondence, BH, Oct 9, 1963; Appellant's Brief, 68133 (Box 10, Folder 28)
      - Appellant's Brief; Complaint, July 15, 1965, 68132 (Box 10, Folder 29)
      - San Francisco MEBA; By-laws (Sea-time), undated; 68131 (Box 10, Folder 30)
      - Correspondence from Mobile, AL, District 1, Local 14, undated; 68130 (Box 10, Folder 31)
      - Tate, Howard PRO MEBA Committee, District 1, undated; 68129 (Box 10, Folder 32)
      - Wirtz, Willard, Department; of Labor v. Pacific Coast National MEBA, 1964, 68128 (Box 10, Folder 33)
      - Pension Fund Suits, 1970, 1984, 68126 (Box 10, Folder 35)
      - Miscellaneous MEBA - Disciplinary, Wage Claims, undated; 68125 (Box 10, Folder 36)
      - Olsen, Odd J., Disability & Pension Rights, undated; 68124 (Box 10, Folder 37)
      - American Marine Engineer, undated; 68123 (Box 10, Folder 38)
      - Pension Plan; Medical Plan, undated; 68122 (Box 10, Folder 39)
      - PROMEBAMEN - Flyers, Press, undated; 68121 (Box 10, Folder 40)
      - Railroads and Tugs, MEBA - Jurisdictional, Disciplinary, undated; 68120 (Box 10, Folder 41)
    - International Organization of Masters, Mates and Pilots (IOMM&P), 68000